
[
  {
    "id": 1,
    "question": "What does the control unit do?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "choice": 1,
        "data": "holds all the registers"
      },
      {
        "choice": 2,
        "data": "performs all the calculations in the CPU"
      },
      {
        "choice": 3,
        "data": "coordinates all the components of the cpu"
      }
    ],
    "topic": "maths",
    "difficulty": "EASY",
    "answer": "coordinates all the components of the cpu"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "What does the arithmetic logic unit do?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "choice": 1,
        "data": "holds the results of arithmatic calculations"
      },
      {
        "choice": 2,
        "data": "performs arithmetic and logical operations on data"
      },
      {
        "choice": 3,
        "data": "coordinates all the components of the CPU"
      }
    ],
    "topic": "Structure and function of the processor",
    "difficulty": "EASY",
    "answer": "performs arithmetic and logical operations on data"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "What does the accumulator do?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "choice": 1,
        "data": "stores the results of the calculations"
      },
      {
        "choice": 2,
        "data": "sends control signals to parts of the CPU"
      },
      {
        "choice": 3,
        "data": "decodes instructions"
      }
    ],
    "topic": "Structure and function of the processor",
    "difficulty": "EASY",
    "answer": "stores the results of the calculations"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "What does the current instruction register do?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "choice": 1,
        "data": "stores all the instructions that are to be executed"
      },
      {
        "choice": 2,
        "data": "stores the address of the current instruction to be executed"
      },
      {
        "choice": 3,
        "data": "it temporarily stores the instruction that is currently being decoded or executed"
      }
    ],
    "topic": "Structure and function of the processor",
    "difficulty": "EASY",
    "answer": "it temporarily stores the instruction that is currently being decoded or executed"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "What does the memory address register do?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "choice": 1,
        "data": "sends address signals to other parts of the CPU"
      },
      {
        "choice": 2,
        "data": "stores memory addresses for data that is being fetched or stored"
      },
      {
        "choice": 3,
        "data": "reads addresses from main memory"
      }
    ],
    "topic": "Structure and function of the processor",
    "difficulty": "EASY",
    "answer": "stores memory addresses for data that is being fetched or stored"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "What does the memory data register do?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "choice": 1,
        "data": "temporarily holds the data that is being transferred to and from memory"
      },
      {
        "choice": 2,
        "data": "stores the address of the next piece of data to be fetched"
      },
      {
        "choice": 3,
        "data": "sends read or write signals to Main memory"
      }
    ],
    "topic": "Structure and function of the processor",
    "difficulty": "EASY",
    "answer": "temporarily holds the data that is being transferred to and from memory"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "Name the three buses in a CPU?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "choice": 1,
        "data": "control, arithmetic, system"
      },
      {
        "choice": 2,
        "data": "data, memory, logic"
      },
      {
        "choice": 3,
        "data": "control, address, data"
      }
    ],
    "topic": "Structure and function of the processor",
    "difficulty": "EASY",
    "answer": "control, address, data"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "What does the address bus do?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "choice": 1,
        "data": "carries memory addresses that identify where the data is being read from or written to"
      },
      {
        "choice": 2,
        "data": "sends read or write signals to Main memory"
      },
      {
        "choice": 3,
        "data": "stores memory addresses for data that is being fetched or stored"
      }
    ],
    "topic": "Structure and function of the processor",
    "difficulty": "EASY",
    "answer": "carries memory addresses that identify where the data is being read from or written to"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "What does the data bus do?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "choice": 1,
        "data": "carries the binary 1's and 0's that make up the actual information being transmitted around the CPU"
      },
      {
        "choice": 2,
        "data": "coordinates all the components of the cpu"
      },
      {
        "choice": 3,
        "data": "sends read or write signals to Main memory"
      }
    ],
    "topic": "Structure and function of the processor",
    "difficulty": "EASY",
    "answer": "carries the binary 1's and 0's that make up the actual information being transmitted around the CPU"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "What does the control bus do?",
    "choices": [
      {
        "choice": 1,
        "data": "controls all the instructions that are fetched"
      },
      {
        "choice": 2,
        "data": "temporarily stores the instruction that is currently being decoded or executed"
      },
      {
        "choice": 3,
        "data": "carries control and command signals to and from every other component of the CPU"
      }
    ],
    "topic": "Structure and function of the processor",
    "difficulty": "EASY",
    "answer": "carries control and command signals to and from every other component of the CPU"
  }
]